,filename,text,text_language,text_english,text_clean,text_english_correct,polarity,subjectivity,text_summary,sentiment,sentiment_score,entity,entity_type
0,data/102730_eng.png,"400 DEATHS GET E-BOOK X AN Corporation ncy Services A municipal worker sprays disinfectant on his colleague after they cremated the body of a man who died due to COVID-19 at a crematorium in Ahmedabad on April 12, 2020. | Photo Credit: REUTERS",en,"400 DEATHS GET E-BOOK X AN Corporation ncy Services A municipal worker sprays disinfectant on his colleague after they cremated the body of a man who died due to COVID-19 at a crematorium in Ahmedabad on April 12, 2020. | Photo Credit: REUTERS","DEATHS GET E - BOOK X AN Corporation Services A municipal worker sprays disinfectant on his colleague after they cremated the body of a man who died due to COVID-19 at a crematorium in Ahmedabad on April , . Photo Credit : REUTERS","400 DEATHS GET E-BOOK X of Corporation ney Services A municipal worker sprays disinfectant on his colleague after they created the body of a man who died due to COVID-19 at a crematorium in Ahmedabad on April 12, 2020. | Photo Credit: REUTERS",-0.125,0.375, A municipal worker sprays disinfectant on his colleague after they cremated the body of,NEGATIVE,0.991692304611206,"['AN Corporation ncy Services', 'Ahmedabad', 'RE', '##UT']","['ORG', 'LOC', 'PER', 'ORG']"
1,data/106349S_por.png,NEWS URGENTE SAMSUNG AO VIVO Rio de Janeiro NOVO MÉTODO DE CONTAGEM PREFEITURA DO RJ EXCLUI 1.177 MORTOS DA ESTATÍSTICA DE COVID-19 G1 SÃO ALVOS DE OPERAÇÃO DA PF CONTRA FAKE NEWS OPERAÇÃO É VISTA NO PLANALTO COM 10:09,pt,"NEWS URGENT SAMSUNG LIVE Rio de Janeiro NEW COUNTING METHOD RJ CITY HALL EXCLUDES 1,177 DEAD FROM COVID-19 STATISTICS G1 ARE TARGET OF PF OPERATION AGAINST FAKE NEWS OPERATION IS SEEN ON THE PLANALTO AT 10:09",NEWS URGENT SAMSUNG LIVE Rio de Janeiro NEW COUNTING METHOD RJ CITY HALL DEAD FROM COVID-19 STATISTICS G1 ARE TARGET OF PF OPERATION AGAINST FAKE NEWS OPERATION IS SEEN ON THE AT,"NEWS URGENT SAMSUNG LIVE Rio de Janeiro NEW COUNTING METHOD of CITY HALL EXCLUDES 1,177 DEAD FROM COVID-19 STATISTICS Of ARE TARGET of of OPERATION AGAINST FAKE NEWS OPERATION of SEEN of THE PLANALTO of 10:09",-0.10681818181818183,0.5886363636363636," NEW COUNTING METHOD RJ City HALL EXCLUDES 1,177 dead",NEGATIVE,0.9906591176986694,"['Rio de Janeiro', 'C', '##IT', 'P', '##NA', '##LTO']","['LOC', 'ORG', 'LOC', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'LOC']"
2,data/102141_2_eng.png,CORONAVIRUS QUARANTINE CORONAVIRUS OUTBREAK BEYOND THIS POINT 2019-nCov Coronavi,en,CORONAVIRUS QUARANTINE CORONAVIRUS OUTBREAK BEYOND THIS POINT 2019-nCov Coronavirus,CORONAVIRUS QUARANTINE CORONAVIRUS OUTBREAK BEYOND THIS POINT - nCov Coronavirus,CORONAVIRUS QUARANTINE CORONAVIRUS OUTBREAK BEYOND THIS POINT 2019-nov Coronavirus,0.0,0.0, Coronavirus QUARANTINE CORONAVIRUS OUTBREAK,NEGATIVE,0.97624671459198,"['CORONAVIRUS', '##AR', '##TI', '##RONAVIR', '##C', 'Co']","['ORG', 'MISC', 'MISC', 'ORG', 'MISC', 'MISC']"
